有什么特别要求吗
Something in particular?
- 葬礼 - 遗憾
- Funeral. - I'm sorry.
不 葬礼 你知道吧
No, funeral, you know?
不 我是说 为你的损失深表遗憾
No, I mean, I'm sorry for your loss.
是啊
Yeah.
那个卖得不错
That's a popular one.
- 过世的是什么人 亲戚? - 不 同事
- Who was it that passed, a relation? - No, we worked together.
- 明白了 工作关系 - 对 工作上的
- I see. A professional relationship. - Yeah, professional.
我是说 我们没那么亲密 但他毕竟是我兄弟
I mean, we wasn't all that tight, but he was still my nigger.
我想我了解了 跟我来
I think I'm on it. Follow me.
靠 这就是我想要的
Hell, yeah, this what I'm talking about.
那把冲锋枪卖得很好
That gat and grip thing over there sells a lot.
我们可以用白色 红色 或粉色康乃馨做
We can do that in white, or red, or pink carnations.
- 粉色? - 粉色衬不起你兄弟?
- Pink? - Your boy was too fierce for the pink?
不 不是那样
No, he wasn't all that.
但当你跟兄弟肩并肩 那就要有始有终...
But when you stand with a nigger, you stand with him to the end...
否则你就不是什么东西
otherwise you ain't nothing yourself.
确实 你兄弟怎么死的
True that. How did your boy fall?
上吊
Hung himself.
活不下去了 吊死了自己
Over at The Cut, strung himself up.
法官发狠 判了他二十年
Judge ran wild on his ass, gave him 20.
瞧 我猜他没法撑这么长
I guess he couldn't handle all those years, you know?
想来他也真是个懦夫 不过...
It's a weak-ass nigger when you think about it.
没理由再抹黑他的名声了
But it ain't no reason to drag his name down no further, you know?
告诉你 给我搞点深色的
I'll tell you what. Let me get something in strong colors.
红色 黑色 无所谓 但要弄得像个大楼...
Red, black, whatever. But make it look like one of the Towers...
你知道 高层区那种
down on Franklin Terrace. You know, the high-rises.
你想用花编个高楼大厦?
You want the arrangement to look like a high-rise housing project?
靠 没错
Hell, yeah.
在前面弄个大大的"221"
And put the numbers 221 in big-ass numbers on the front.
行吗 他曾有段时间执掌Fremont大楼
All right? He used to have that Fremont Tower for a while.
"221" 好的 还有什么想说的
221, all right. Anything else you want it to say?
比如?
Like what?
"安息" "缅怀" 诸如此类的?
"Rest in peace," "In Remembrance," something like that?
一些表达哀思的文字
Something that says how you feel about the loss.
去他的吧 只要...
Look, man, fuck it, all right? Just...
只要把那大楼弄得像模像样就行 懂吗
Just make sure the Towers look like they do, all right?
好了 谢了
All right. Thanks.
火线重案组 第二季 第七集 余波未平
The Wire S02E07 Backwash
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* He's got the fire and the fury *
* At his command *
* Well you don't have to worry *
* If you hold on to Jesus hand *
* We'll all be safe from Satan *
* When the thunder rolls *
* Just gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
"别担心 小子 你还在上班"  ---"马面"
- 你复制了个什么 - 电脑
- You cloned a what? - A computer.
这样我们能实时监控卸货...
We can watch how the cargo comes off the ship in real time...
追踪走私品 查出去向
try to follow the contraband, see where it leads.
我们每月办25件谋杀案 就像个战地医院...
We're running a 25-murder-a-month MASH Unit here...
你们却想慢慢来 做个脑外科手术
and you guys wanna slow things down a bit, and do a bit of brain surgery.
Rawls要是经过 看见你俩...
If Rawls comes walking through here and sees the two of you hunched over...
放着14件谋杀案不查 弯腰打电动 他会抓狂
playing video games on 14 open murders, he's gonna blow!
正因此我们才请求Daniels...
That is exactly why we asked Lt. Daniels...
给我们在他那东南区的小驻地腾个地方
to set us up at his off-site, over in the southeast.
他们在查码头工人别的事 大部分跟毒品有关
They're looking at the dock boys for other shit, drugs mostly.
- Daniels 原来缉毒科那个? - 对
- Daniels, who used to be in Narcotics? - Yeah.
如果Daniels已经建立了一个专案组 也许他会受理这些谋杀案
If Daniels has a detail set up already, maybe he takes the murders, too.
他又不是傻子 Jay 他只答应给我们一间小黑屋
He ain't no fool, Jay. He's just giving us a room with no view.
那算是同意了吧 他同意我们继续调查了
That was approval, right? He gave approval to go ahead with this.
不知道
I don't know.
接下来怎么办
What's next?
接下来我们要让那些码头工人 以为我们不查了
Next is for us to get them dock boys back to thinking that we've gone away.
我是说 我用大陪审团 搞得他们疑神疑鬼
I mean, we spooked them right good with that grand jury shit.
如果我们要对付他们 得让他们觉得...
If we're gonna set up on them, they need to think...
我们已经不构成威胁了
we ain't gonna be a problem no more.
怎样才能让他们那样想呢
How are they gonna think that?
不 你得理解 生意不是那样做的
No, see, that ain't the way it works.
不是
It ain't.
因为每天在外头碰运气的是我 不是吗?
'Cause I'm the one out here all day taking the chance, right?
要是警察出现 吃官司的可不是你
Police roll up into this bitch, it ain't gonna be you that catch no charge.
所以 还是聪明点 你该做的...
So, least-wise, the thing you need to do...
就是把货均分 给我们分销
is lay all that good shit down on an even split.
到周五 我和手下把货卖掉...
Come Friday, me and my niggers done sold all that shit off...
你过来拿钱 这就是我的经营方式
you come past and get paid. That's how I'm at with it.
嘿 Frog
Hey, Frog.
过来
Come here.
说真的 过来
No, seriously. Come here.
我得说 我不知道该怎样说...
First of all, and I don't know how to tell you this...
才能不伤害你感情
without hurting you deeply...
首先
first of all,
你毕竟是个白人
you happen to be white.
我是说Rapolla街土生土长的白人...
I'm talking raised-on-Rapolla-Street white...
你老妈曾拖着你去圣Casimir教堂...
where your mama used to drag you down to St. Casimir's...
就像那个街区的其他小屁孩一样
just like all the other little pisspants on the block.
其次 我也是白人
Second, I'm also white.
不是个混迹街角 微不足道的白人...
Not hang-on-the-corner- don't-give-a-fuck white...
而是Locust区码头工会47分会的白人
but Locust-Point-I.B.S. - Local-47 white.
不签合同 我就不干活...
I don't work without no fucking contract...
也不会像我的表弟Ziggy...
and I don't stand around listening to horseshit excuses...
对一些烂借口买账 顺便一说...
like my cousin Ziggy, who, by the way...
你和你那些耍小聪明的 街头混混还欠他钱呢
is still owed money by you and all your down, street-wise whiggers.
你先掏掏口袋 预付500...
You go in your pocket, come up with $500 in advance...
再把你欠Zig的210块还上...
and the $210 that you owe to Zig...
我的货就交你卖了
you can work my package.
这是你上周放出的货 让Moochie大攒了一笔?
This is the shit you had out here last week. The dimes that Moochie was slinging?
那是上等货 Moochie很快就卖光了
The shit was good. Moochie sold out quick.
好吧
All right.
我是说 我会让手下拿钱过来
I'm saying, I'm gonna send my man around with the dollars.
做你自己
Keep it real.
随便啦
Whatever.
都还满意吗
Everything to your satisfaction?
嗯 干得不错
Yeah, you on it.
监狱里的人都认为他是自杀的吧
Prison people taking it that that boy hung his own self, right?
看样子是
Seems so.
我表弟做事一向干净利索
My cousin always works clean.
我知道不关我事...
None of my business, I know...
我只是想问问Avon知道这事吗
but did your man Avon even know about it?
你自作主张?
You're on your own here?
你说得对
You're right.
不关你事
It ain't none of your business.
我是你的话...
And if I were you...
我也不会把这事传到Avon耳朵里
I wouldn't want a word of this mess up in Avon's ear.
Baltimore兄弟不会受任何牵连 我发誓
Baltimore niggers off the hook. I swear.
所有人
All y'all.
趁热吃吧 味道不错
You better get up in this before it get cold. This shit is good.
伙计 那屁事不怪你 真的
My man, that bullshit ain't on you. It ain't, man.
你知道 在这里 D也该清楚只能靠自己
Up in here, D knew he had to stand on his own. You know this.
靠 去他的
Man, fuck him.
他知道他上吊我们要承受什么
He knew when he hung himself how we was gonna carry it.
他知道他那么做了 我们会有一刻像现在这样
He knew when he did that, that we were gonna be in a moment like this, right now.
他很清楚
He knew that.
那小子那么做是要伤害我 伙计
That nigger did that shit to hurt me, man.
但 你知道 D他妈的太脆弱了
But, you know, man, D was just fucking weak.
在他还是个孩子时我就带他出道
I tried to crimp him along since he was a shorty, nigger.
我把他带大 为他铺路...
I tried to bring him up, bring him along...
- 你对他确实很好 - 没错
- You were real good to him. - I was.
这事很让人伤心 确实如此
Man, it's sad, what happened. That shit is sad.
但这孩子上次差点卖了你
But the boy almost rolled on you that one time.
你知道 他会想他挨不了那么多年...
You know, he get to thinking he can't do the years in here...
可能会再次出卖你 谁知道呢
he might've could've rolled again. Who knows?
我是说...
I'm just saying...
这可能对大家都好
it might've been for the best, you know?
大伙都叫他"头"..."戆头"
His name is Head. Dick Head.
看这个
Check this out.
把手指放这儿
Put your finger right there.
- 不错 - 不错吧
- Nice. - Nice, right?
- 两位 - 我们要买窃听器
- Fellows. - We need a bug.
能承受现代都市...
Something that can stand up to the pressures...
犯罪环境压力的窃听器
of the modern urban crime environment.
过来看看
Let me show you.
两位 这可是个好东西 比点22口径的子弹都小
Okay, fellows, this is the real deal. Smaller than a 22.
讯号清晰 结实耐用
And it's got a clear channel. Sturdy as hell.
放在在谈话者10英尺内...
You get this bad boy within 10 feet of any conversation...
就跟听Chuck Thompson(巴尔的摩体育广播员)解说比赛一样清楚
it sounds like Chuck Thompson doing play-by-play.
- 多少 - 1500块
- How much? - $1,500.
但看在你们是警察的份上 打个折 1250块
But seeing as you're sworn officers, the police discount drops it to $1,250.
- 你买吗 - 我买吗
- You in? - Am I in?
他刚刚说的可是1250块 Herc
The man just said $1,250, Herc.
我们能测试一下吗
Can we give it a test run?
在现代都市犯罪环境中测试吗
A test drive in the modern urban crime environment?
可以 信用卡留下 让你带走48小时
Yeah, leave me your credit card and take it for 48 hours.
改主意了 可以退货
Change your mind, bring it back. No problem.
- 我跟我搭档商量一下 - 好的
- Let me consult my partner. - Of course.
你有信用卡吗
You got a credit card?
- 你没有? - 刷爆了
- Don't you? - It's maxed to the max, man.
我们做诱捕有段时间了...
We've been doing hand-to-hands for a while now...
在那些角落没法再有新进展了
and we ain't no higher up on the ladder and on those corners.
我们就拿去用两天  达到目的了就还回来
We're just gonna use it for a couple days, get what we need, and bring it back.
我只是给你手下找个地方
I gave your man some room, that's all.
你给他找了个家
You gave him a home.
Moreland警探的目标跟你们一样
Det. Moreland's target looks to be the same as yours.
- 不 - 一样
- No. - Yes.
你接下这14件谋杀案...
You could take these 14 homicides...
能把你半吊子的专案组 整成真像那么回事
and turn that half-assed detail you got going into something that matters.
说实话 你解决了谋杀案 为那些统计数字我会爱死你
I'll be honest. You solve the murders, I'll love you for the stats.
你解决不了 也让凶杀科...
And if you don't, I've made it so the Homicide Unit...
不至于承受过低的破案率
doesn't have to bear the whole brunt of a lower clearance rate.
在我看来这是双赢
It's win-win for me.
- 不 - 拜托 警督
- No. - Come on, Lieutenant.
此恩日后一定报答
A good turn here will not be forgotten.
我只是想做些简单明了的工作 让自己离开地下室
I'm trying to dig myself out of the basement with something simple and clean here.
逮些毒贩 运气好再逮些卖淫的...
Drug arrests, maybe a prostitution bust if I get lucky...
Burrell就答应把我调离地下室
and I'm out from under with Burrell.
抱歉 警监
Sorry, Colonel.
谋杀案你留着吧 我不搅这浑水
You keep the murders, and my ass stays covered.
比看上去聪明
Smarter than he looks.
- 你朋友呢 - 你说谁
- Where's your friend? - Who's that?
- 那个黑人 凶杀科那个 - 据我所知结案了
- The black fellow, the Homicide guy. - Case is done, for all I know.
是吗
Yeah?
你们什么都不招 船上那些也是
You all didn't go for nothing, and no one on the ship did either.
所以他让我回来了 自己去办新案子
So, he sent me back and moved on to new business.
- 这么说你又跟以往一样了? - 嗯 跟以往一样
- So you back to the usual then? - Yeah, the usual.
只是我不会再常到 Patapsco或North Point巡逻了
Except I won't be around Patapsco or North Point much.
明天开始 我要去Fairfield站
Starting tomorrow, I'm down at the Fairfield Terminals.
Fairfield?
对 上面希望在那边的化工厂 多派辆巡逻车
Yeah, bosses want another car patrolling the chemical plants.
我猜跟恐怖分子有关吧
Because of terrorism, I guess.
你太漂亮了 去Fairfield码头太可惜了 亲爱的
You're too pretty for the Fairfield Piers, darling.
你该在这儿跟我们一块
You need to be uptown here with us.
你在西南区升了官...
You got stripes in the Southeast...
却不能用Valchek的监控车 为他的专案组工作?
and can't pull Valchek's spy van to work his own detail?
伙计 那车我连鬼影都没见着
Man, I've never seen that thing.
- 藏起来 - 像条小虫
- Snug. - As a bug.
裹在小毯里
In a rug.
出发
Let's go.
- 这东西让人昏昏欲睡 - 还很无聊
- This shit is hypnotic. - Boring, too.
你去演了出戏?
You make a show of it?
让工作的人都看见我在巡逻车里
Let everyone working see me in that radio car.
那是Valparaiso号?
Is that the Valparaiso?
它不是Talco航运公司的船 "马面"不在上面作业
It ain't a Talco Line ship, doesn't have Horseface working.
看它卸了半天货 估计也是白忙
Probably wasting half a day watching it offload.
- 就是 我们现在该在酒吧了 - 没白忙
- Yeah, we should be at the bar by now. - Nothing's wasted.
我找到点感觉了 弄明白了正常的运作
I've been getting a feel for this shit. How it plays and works without the dirt.
- 当他们丢了个集装箱... - 我就会发现
- So when they lose a can... - I see it go.
鹿特丹:未来货运管理已成型
先生们 女士们
Gentlemen. Ladies.
未来从此开始
The future is now.
为在爆发式的全球经济中输送物资...
To bring goods to an exploding global economy...
做到更快 更便宜 更安全...
and to deliver those goods faster, cheaper and safer...
世界最大的港口 鹿特丹 采用现代机器人技术
modern robotics do much of the work in the world's largest seaport, Rotterdam.
物流是荷兰的传统强项...
Moving cargo is a traditional strength of the Dutch...
较之世上其他港口 他们用 更少的人力运输更多的货物
who shuttle more freight in fewer man-hours than any port in the world.
现在 荷兰人向我们 展示货物管理的未来
And now, the Dutch have modeled the future of cargo management.
在三分之一英里长的船上...
Completely containerized cargo arrives and departs...
全集装箱式运输货物装卸 一天二十四小时 周期更短
on ships a third of a mile long, 24 hours a day, with short turnaround.
智能卡技术提供了更好的安全性...
Smart card technology provides greater security...
增强了可靠性  不用枉费欠可靠的人力监控
and improved accountability, with no need for unreliable human surveillance.
Frog 伙计 我们就少了五支的钱
Frog, man, we light five caps is all, man.
我是说 你太斤斤计较了 明白吗
I'm saying, you getting all ridiculous over bits and pieces. You feeling me?
不 伙计 这是原则问题
Nigger, it's the principle of the thing.
就像你在商店当收银员...
It's like you in a store working the register...
一天结束 就得把钱加一块
and at the end of the day, the shitjust add up.
Mad Dog明天要来收余款...
Mad Dog gonna roll through here tomorrow with the re-up...
至少这次我得让钱够数
and I want to have the package right for once.
嘿 Carver
Hey, Carver.
难道技术不是个炸弹吗
Isn't technology the fucking bomb?
...而全球定位系统指导每个集装箱...
...and global positioning systems guide each container...
各就其位 在甲板或码头...
to its proper spot, on board or on the docks...
同时最先进的电脑 追踪每个码头的装运...
while state-of-the-art-computers track shipments in every part...
部分你们所见的系统已升级
Some of the systems you're seeing have already been upgraded.
鹿特丹现在的年吞吐量为3亿5千万吨...
Rotterdam now works 350 million tons of cargo annually...
把新加坡远远甩开
leaving Singapore a distant second.
那里的工人工时有多少
What kind of man-hours are the stevedores clocking over there?
我手头没有这方面数据 抱歉
I don't have those figures handy. I'm sorry.
但鹿特丹的确雇佣了4000人
But Rotterdam does employ 4,000 people.
4000人一年装卸3亿5千万吨?
4,000 people to move 350 million tons a year?
- 没错 - 很有效率 Nat
- That's right. - That's efficiency, Nat.
因为排除了一些高危工作...
By eliminating some of the more dangerous work...
鹿特丹的新技术使得...
the Rotterdam technologies have reduced...
雇工工伤事故降低了60%
employee work-related accidents and injuries by 60%.
这是我们乐意看到的 不是吗
I think we can all be happy with that, can't we?
有问题吗 请说
Question? Yes?
那些GPS读数 它们是否...
The GPS readings, are they exact...
不作业当然不会有工伤 不是吗
You can't get hurt if you ain't working, right?
不 能用于任何货运 适应任何天气
No, they work with all kinds of cargo, in all kinds of weather.
来了
Coming.
- 嘿 Jackie - String 你也送吃的?
- Hey, Jackie. - String. You, too?
我们收到的食物够吃上三周了
We got enough food for three weeks right now.
Brianna还好吗 她在里面?
How's Brianna? Is she back there?
你好吗 小家伙?
What's up, little man?
你感觉怎么样
How you holding up?
Bri
Bri.
Brianna
- Nicky你这周拿到工时了吗 - 没有
- Nicky boy, you get days this week? - No.
周四有四艘船 你至少能做一天
Four ships on Thursday. You could've pulled a day for sure.
这是上两批货你的五成 还有你那批Frog欠你的
That's your half on the last two packages, plus what Frog owed you on your own shit.
都在这了 小子
It's all there, cuz.
- 你他妈哪根筋不对了 笑脸君? - 没什么
- What the fuck is wrong with you, smiley? - Nothing.
Frog怎么说
What did Frog say?
"这是额外的几百块 把那小白痴哄开心点"?
"Here's a couple of hundred extra, make the little goof happy"?
那批货是我自己的事 Nick
The packages were my thing, Nick.
靠 你要是不管更好
Fuck, if you ain't handle that business better, too.
Zig 我们在赚钱了
Zig, we're making money.
那是你赚的 Nicky
It's your move, Nicky.
去他的 我现在还有别的事要烦呢
Fuck it. I got other issues right now.
亲子鉴定?
Paternity?
Priscilla Katlow
Priscilla Katlow.
老天 Zig 你搞大了Prissy Katlow的肚子?
Jesus, Zig. You knocked up Prissy Katlow?
就上了一次
I only fucked her once.
老天 这儿的每个人都跟她有一腿
Christ, everybody down the point fucked her the once.
你怎么知道孩子是你的
How do you know it's yours?
跟这律师联系过了?
You call this lawyer?
我想我该先把自己灌醉
Figured I'd get drunk first.
好主意
That's a good plan.
- 有俄国人吗 - 很多女孩 都很漂亮
- Russians? - Lot of girls. Pretty ones.
大部分都有外来口音
Most of them had some kind of accent anyway.
Shardene的朋友给的情报不错 里面谁在负责
Shardene's friend hooked us up good. Who's in charge?
我想是俱乐部的人
You got the club people, I guess.
还有个我看见走进后厢房的女人
And there's some woman I've seen go into the back room.
看上去略年长
She looks a little bit older.
我没法凑过去跟她搭话
I couldn't get close enough to say much about her.
约40岁
She looks about 40.
有调戏谁吗 Prez?
Grab any ass, Prez?
我是说 为了我们 我想清楚了
What I'm saying is, I've sorted it out for us.
- 真的 - 为了我们?
- I have. - For us?
我还在地下室时 辞职是合理的 真的
When I was in the basement, it made sense to quit. It did.
但一旦Burrell肯拉我一把...
But once Burrell reached out...
但你忤逆过Burrell  他不会就这么不计前嫌吧?
But Burrell is the one that you crossed. He's not likely to forget that, is he?
更别提他还清楚你过去那些烂事了
Not to mention what he knows about you from the bad old days.
比你年轻一半的蠢货都 可以当警长或警监了...
Fools half your age are gonna be Major and Colonel...
你却还惦记着破一两件案就能自救
and you'll still think that scratching out a case or two will save you.
我知道这不是案子的问题
It isn't about the casework, I know that.
就在今天 Rawls还让我去刑侦科...
Just today, Rawls calls me up to CID...
让我接手他的集装箱女尸案
asks me to take his homicides from the dead girls on that shipping container.
我告诉他 没门 那案子没法破
I told him, no shot. That case is a loser.
如果我这次小心行事...
If I'm looking out for number one...
按Burrell的要求办事...
I'm gonna bring Burrell exactly what he asked for...
给他能打发Stan Valchek的调查结果
and exactly what he needs to make Stan Valchek go away.
不多不少 我这次是按他们的游戏规则
No more, no less. I'm playing their game this time.
听着 你想在疏通运河 的事上冒险是一回事
Look, it's one thing you taking a run at this dredging thing.
像你这种疯子 就随你吧...
Fucked-up as you are, we can let that slide for a while...
但你这个要求就太过分了
but now, you're asking too much.
再一年 Nat
One more year, Nat.
- 不是为了我 是为了整个工会 - 选举已经安排好了
- Not for me, for the fucking union. - The election's been scheduled.
你知道我们去年投了你...
You knew last year, when we gave you the votes...
这次该轮到Ott了 你心里有数
that this time would be Ott's turn. You knew that.
那Ott可以等下次 连任两届
So Ott runs next time. He'll take that year and the next.
该我们坐庄了 Frank
It's our turn, Frank.
黑人白人有什么区别 Nat?
Black, White, what's the difference, Nat?
河道疏通不了 我们都是黑鬼 不好意思说了粗口
Until we get that fucking canal dredged, we're all niggers, pardon my French.
或是波兰仔 失礼我也说了
Or Polacks, pardon mine.
你知道我的意思 我不是针对Ott
You know what I'm saying, this ain't about Ott.
我只求多一年完成我开始的工作 一年就好
I just want one more year to finish what I started here.
然后由Ott连任两届财务秘书 没问题
Then Ott stays Secretary-Treasurer for the next two, no problem.
想想吧
Think about it.
- 喂? - Brucie宝贝
- Hello? - Brucie, baby.
- Frankie Sobotka 最近可好 - 你跟审裁委员谈过了吗
- Frankie Sobotka, how's it hanging? - You talk to the presiding officers yet?
很多女孩 很多保镖
Lot of girls. Lot of muscle.
Zig 老天 离我远点 混蛋
Zig, Jesus, get off me, you jerk.
等等 Zig
Yo, Zig
你什么时候收到的?
When did you get served with these?
今早的邮件
I got them in the mail this morning.
邮件里?
In the mail?
对 今早
Yeah, this morning.
当初Pokey Barber收到亲子鉴定要求...
When Pokey Barber got hit with paternity...
是治安官亲自把文件送上门
a sheriff had to come to his house and serve him with papers.
Dolores 我能用酒吧电话吗
Dolores, can I use the bar phone?
- 你打给谁 - 这狗屁上面署名的律师
- Who are you calling? - The lawyer on this piece of bullshit.
什么 三更半夜还有哪个律师事务所营业
What? Ain't no fucking law firm open in the middle of the goddamn night.
讼棍和骗子忽悠事务所
Shyster, Shyster and Shyster.
- 他耍你 Zig - 谁耍了我
- He got you, Zig. - Who got me?
是Maui?
Maui?
唱的是首流行歌"私生子"
* Love child, never meant to be *
* Love child, born in poverty *
大堂没有公厕 如果你未受邀造访...
There's no restroom in the lobby, and if you're not an approved visitor...
我不能让你进去
I just don't have the authorization.
好吧
Okay.
告诉我 如果你急了去哪解决
Tell me something. When you have to go, where do you go?
不好意思 先生 您是住客吗
Excuse me, sir? Are you a resident?
抱歉 走错门了
Sorry. Wrong building.
都上了六楼
Sixth floor, all of them.
Thomas "马面" Pakusa
Thomas "Horseface" Pakusa.
内定将在Talco公司的Esmeralda号上作业
Slated to be the ship-runner on Talco Line's Esmeralda.
货船预计明日中午抵达 Patapsco中转站6号船台
ETA, noon tomorrow, Berth 6, Patapsco Terminal.
- 有进展了 - 我们需要监视车
- So we're on. - We're gonna need help with surveillance.
尤其是在港口 他们都认识我们了
On the docks especially, since our faces are known down there.
我大概能把Greggs和Prez找来一起查
I can reach out to Greggs and Prez, maybe. Bring them in on it.
不告诉警督吗
Should we tell the Lieutenant?
目前 对于他被扯进谋杀案调查...
Right now, the less he knows he's involved in the murder investigation...
他知道得越少越开心
the happier he'll feel.
新车?
New truck?
管他呢 我们有钱赚不是吗
What the fuck, we're making money here, right?
- 该死 没错 - 就是
- Hell, yeah. - For real.
这家伙是供货人 拍下车牌号
This guy's some kind of supplier. Snap some shots of the truck tags.
- 有新货吗 - 你有钱我就有货 不是吗
- You got more for me? - I got ifyou got for me, right?
不得不说 你的货很紧俏 很久以来都没这么好的
Got to say, your thing is tight. Best around here in a long while.
靠
Fuck!
我会跟你继续合作 伙计...
I'm with you on this, man...
好的 小子
All right, dawg.
不 该死
Oh,fuck me
拜托 混账 你他妈哪根筋不对了
Come on, asshole, what the fuck's wrong with you?
快开走
Keep it fucking moving.
老天爷
Jesus Christ!
不
No!
我向警用无线电系统要了6频道
I cleared it with KGA, we'll be working off of Channel 6.
Prez 你盯着外出的卡车道
Prez, you got the eyeball on the outbound truck gate.
做好跟入Broening高速公路任意方向的准备
Need you to set up so you can move in either direction on Broening Highway.
Bunk 你在Newkirk和Broening待命
Bunk, you set up on Newkirk and Broening.
我和Russell盯着电脑 剩下港口就交给Kima
Me and Russell will be on the computer. That leaves the terminal itself to Kima.
他们可能不认识我 但我肯定不能在那瞎晃
They might not know my face, but I sure as shit can't hang down there.
我想我该向缉毒科借CG&E卡车(维修公司)
I'm thinking I should borrow that CG&E truck from Narcotics.
戴个安全帽 拿个笔记板
Slap on a hard hat, pick up a clipboard.
如果他们这次不偷东西怎么办
What if they're not sneaking anything off this time? What then?
那你只好悲剧地再浪费一天...
Tragically, you will have wasted another day in a life you've already misspent...
你已经浪费在Baltimore警察机关的生命了
in the service of the city of Baltimore.
- 里面不是活物了吧 - 如果他们不尽快取走...
- Nothing's alive in these, right? - Lf they don't go hot to a truck...
你就送回货堆敲一敲确定一下
you go back in the stacks and bang on them to make sure.
我不相信这帮希腊杂种
I trust these Greek fucks with nothing.
- 你怎么样 - 很好
- How you hanging? - Good. I'm good.
你最近没干多少活
You ain't been working much.
注意点 Nick 别做些我不会做的事
Stay close, Nick. Don't do anything I wouldn't do.
* Jesus on the main line *
* Tell him what you want *
* Oh, Jesus on the main line *
* Jesus on the main line *
* Tell him what you want *
* Call him up and tell him what you want *
* lf you want salvation *
* Tell him what you want *
* Oh, if you want salvation *
* lf you want salvation *
* Tell him what you want *
* Call him up and tell him what you want *
* Oh, call him up, call him up *
* Tell him what you want *
* Call him up, call him up *
* Jesus on the main... *
* ...line now *
那个221楼你送的?
You did the 221?
很有型
Shit look tight.
节哀顺变
Sorry for the loss.
不过葬礼办得不错
You all sent him off right, though.
跟我参加过的一个办得一样好
As good a homecoming as I been to.
- 我知道你分担了痛苦 - 无疑
- You been to your share, man, I know. - No doubt.
当然 现在不是时候也不是地方...
Of course, this is neither the time nor the place...
但我还是想跟你谈谈
but I thought I might get at you for a moment.
- 我有个提议 - 你先到车那边等着 伙计
- Got a proposition here. - Go ahead to the car, man.
请原谅我话里得罪的地方
Ain't exactly talking out of turn when I say...
不过 西区的货色烂了不是一两天了
that, uh, Westside dope been weak for a while now.
城里每个毒友都知道 Avon卖得都是些垃圾
Every dope fiend in the city knows that Avon been putting out piss, calling it shit.
问题是 你们手头有市里最好的地盘
The thing is, y'all sitting on some of the best real estate in the city.
高楼区 平房区 街角
The Terrace, the low-rises, the avenue corners.
我知道你以有自己的 一套说话方式著称...
Respecting the fact that you're known to have a way with your words...
但你什么时候才能说些我不知道的
when are you gonna tell me something I don't know?
那我说重点 我的货很正 String
Let me put a point on it. My shit is right, String.
我从外面直接弄进Baltimore 那些货都是没掺的
I got dope coming straight into Baltimore, and the shit is raw.
85-90%的纯度 你知道这是事实
85, 90%. And you know it's true.
西区的一半的瘾君子 一天上两次Fallsway...
You got half the Westside coming over to Fallsway twice a day...
因为东区的货强过西区太多
because Eastside dope be kicking the shit out of Westside dope.
- 你们有路子? - 这些货都是直接下船的
- You connected? - This shit is straight off the damn boat.
除了可卡因 我都不用上纽约了 没必要
I ain't even going to New York except for my coke. Ain't no need.
事实上 你们有最好的地盘却没货源
Thing is, y'all got the best territory, and no kind of product.
我有最好的货 但要更多的地盘...
I got the best product, but could stand a little more territory...
你也知道该怎么做了
so you see where this thing needs to go.
你也知道Avon为拿下高层区 付出了多少心血
Now you know Avon fought real hard for them Towers.
我们搞定了Rayford兄弟和 Big Dennis Woodson 我是说...
We took down the Rayford brothers, Big Dennis Woodson, I mean...
生意归生意 String 低买高卖
This shit is just business, String. Buy for a dollar, sell for two.
生意就该这么做 你有高层区 我有他们想要的货
That's all it need be. You got the Towers, I got what goes in them.
其他都是屁话
Later for all that bullshit.
- 我会和Avon谈谈的 - 记得谈
- I'll talk to Avon. - You do that.
拜托 我读得懂预算汇总 没有资金用在疏通运河上
Come on, I can read a budget summary. There's nothing in there for dredging.
财政赤字 政府要限制公债
Shortfall in revenues. The governor's looking to limit bond issues.
- 但有粮食码头项目 - 而其他的只是讨论而已?
- But the grain pier is still in there. - And the rest is just talk?
讨论是好事 Frank 讨论是个开始
Talk is good, Frank. Talk is a start.
游说是你该死的工作
Talk is your fucking job description.
哇啦哇啦哇啦
Yak. Yak. Yak. Blah. Blah. Blah.
就像说你那些检验员的工作 是把数字输入电脑而已
That's like saying all the checkers do is punch numbers into a computer.
你儿子
Your son,
最大那个 他在哪读书?
the oldest one, he goes to what school?
- Jason在普林斯顿 - 普林斯顿
- Jason's at Princeton. - Princeton.
他毕业后会做什么
And after he graduates, he's gonna do what?
- 随他喜欢 - 是啊
- Whatever he wants. - Right.
你把他送到普林斯顿 让他做自己想做的工作
You sent him to Princeton to do whatever the fuck he wants.
当我们还是孩子时...
You know, back when we were kids...
Danny Hared的父亲从船上偷了几瓶干邑
Danny Hare's father stole a couple cases of cognac off a ship.
回到家后却发现不是干邑 而是果珍
Except when he gets it home, it ain't cognac, it's Tang.
- 果珍? - 刚发明的
- Tang? - Just invented.
电视上说宇航员奔月的时候喝这个
TV said it's what the astronauts drank on their way to the moon.
- 你要喝了... - 你也能成为宇航员
- You drink it... - You could be an astronaut, too.
整个夏天 Hare的孩子们就喝这个
All summer long, that shit was all the Hare kids drank.
早餐喝果珍 中午喝果珍...
Tang with breakfast, Tang with lunch...
半夜吓醒都喝果珍
Tang when they woke up scared in the middle of the night.
你觉得他们长大后做什么?
What do you think they grew up to be?
码头工 你怎么想
Stevedores. What the fuck you think?
我觉得Jason DiBiago长大后...
Something tells me Jason DiBiago will grow up...
就跟他老爸一样会敛财
and squeeze a buck the way his old man did.
你过分了 Frank
You're out of line, Frank.
我曾祖父是磨刀的
My great-grandfather was a knife sharpener.
推着块磨刀石从Preston街 走到Alice-Ann街...
Pushed a grinding stone up Preston Street to Alice-Ann...
因为给轮胎打气  一条腿长一条腿短
one leg shorter than the other from pumping the wheel.
他不想让他儿子再推磨刀石...
Since he didn't want his sons to push the goddamn thing...
他让我祖父读完了高中...
he made sure my grandfather finished high school...
而我爸则考进了大学
and my old man went to any college that would take him.
你跟我聊过去是吧
You're talking history, right?
我说的是现在
I'm talking now.
在你有孩子前 人们会问"你老爸是谁"
Down here, it's still: "Who's your old man?" 'Til you got kids of your own.
接着就是 "你儿子是谁"
Then it's, "Who's your son?"
但看完今天那部恐怖电影后 我会说... 机器人
But after the horror movie I've seen today... Robots!
码头到处都是机器人
Piers full of robots!
我儿子从现在开始要还能 输五年数字就算走运了
My kid will be lucky if he's punching numbers five years from now.
我能不能那把菜刀给DiBiago 和他后代磨 关我屁事
While it don't mean shit that I can't take my steak knives to DiBiago and sons...
我伤心的是海边没有Sobotkas的未来
it breaks my heart that there's no future for the Sobotkas on the waterfront.
Robert Irsay 原巴尔的摩著名橄榄球教练 后来把球队带到了Indianapolis
给你 Brucie 我想它们是你的"尺寸"
Here, Brucie. I think they're your size.
我继续经营是因为 我相信你会不断努力...
I'm operating under the assumption that because of your relentless diligence...
让为粮食码头拨款的议案通过
the funding for the grain pier is gonna pass the assembly.
但我会继续提运河 你也要继续提运河...
But I'm also talking about the canal. So you're gonna talk about the canal...
让执掌本州的政客也谈起运河...
the Muldoons who run the old line state are gonna talk about it...
知道那鬼东西某天 以某种方式得以疏通...
until some day, some way, that motherfucker gets dredged...
让我们的船能够进来
and we get some ships in here.
放下来
Bring it down!
有个消失了
Got one that disappeared.
集装箱号有吗
Get the container number?
- 11-37呼叫12-14 - 请讲 Lester
- 11-37 to 12-14. - Go ahead, Lester.
- 有个消失了 准备好记下了吗 - 说吧
- We got one, you prepared to copy? - Send it.
Z T G R...
Zulu, Tango, Golf, Romeo...
9 7 3 2 6 5 校验数9
9, 7, 3, 2, 6, 5, check digit 9.
收到 我看到了
Copy that, I've got it in the yard.
- 11-99 - 11-99听到
- 11-99. - 11-99.
有动静了 准备好
We got a live one. Be up.
- 我要注意什么? - 待命
- What am I looking for? - Stand by on that.
报告 我看见一个白人男性 橙色安全背心...
Be advised, I've got a White male, orange safety vest...
蓝色工作裤
blue overalls.
他正把车连在... 那东西怎么说来着
He's hooking the truck onto the... What do you call it?
收到 接下来呢
Copy that. What next?
要么司机开过检查站...
One of two things. The driver takes it through checkout...
这样的话可能是"马面" 入错了集装箱号...
in which case it may be that Horseface entered the wrong container number...
会在那里被发现 要么直接开出车道
and they find it there. Or it goes out to Bobtail Lane.
如果那么做 就是偷了
If it does that, they're doing the dirt.
11-37呼叫12-14
11-37 to 12-14.
Kima 盯紧了 直到他离开堆场
Kima, keep the eyeball until it clears the yard.
如果它停在检查站或径直出去就报告
Advise if it stops at the checkout point, or goes straight out.
收到
Copy.
12-14 他绕过了检查站 完毕
12-14. He went around the checkout. Copy.
- 11-37呼叫11-99 - 99收到
- 11-37 to 11-99. - 99.
目标正向你开来 看见没有
Target's coming at you, you see it?
在Broening发现目标 正往西驶向市区
I got him on Broening, heading west towards the city.
收到 11-37呼叫11-34
Copy, 11-37 to 11-34.
- 目标抵达你的位置 - 11-34收到
- Target approaching your 20. - 11-34, copy that.
他径直驶向Newkirk
I got him going straight on Newkirk.
- 到你了 Bunk - 收到
- He's all yours, Bunk. - Copy.
- 11-34 你盯紧了 - 收到
- 11-34, you got the eyeball. - Copy.
- 11-34呼叫 - 请说 34
- 11-34. - Go ahead, 34.
他驶进Newkirk路旁空地了 有个仓库
He went to ground off of Newkirk. Some kind of warehouse.
等等 我掉个头 看看门牌
Wait one. I'll swing back, get a 20.
报告 是个仓库
Be advised, it is a warehouse.
金字塔公司 Newkirk路5605号
Pyramid Inc. 5605 Newkirk.
收到
Copy that.
Brianna责怪你?
Brianna, man, she putting it on you?
Avon 你知道他在吸毒?
Avon, you knew he was using?
我知道 但没亲眼看见
I seen it, but I didn't see it.
我是说 他染上毒瘾...
I mean, he came up off that shit...
接着我们就利用那警卫做了那事 我以为...
then we did our thing with the guard, and I thought...
该死
Fuck.
我们把他的告别式办了 伙计 我是说 办得不错
We did our thing with the homegoing, man. I mean, it came off nice.
- 是吗 - 嗯 大家都到场了
- Yeah? - Yeah, everybody showed.
- Brianna怎么样了 - 不好过
- How did Brianna do? - Rough.
没人希望这事发生
Don't nobody want shit like this to happen, man.
如果我早知道那孩子会轻生...
If I'd have known the boy was gonna be doing shit like that...
- 你懂我意思吗 - 监狱里的人怎么说
- you know what I mean? - What are the prison people saying?
他就那样把自己勒死了?
That he just hung himself like that?
就是把绳子绕在门把上 然后坐在地上
Just tied a rope around a knob, and sat his ass down.
一个人想那样做 谁阻止得了?
How the fuck you gonna stop a man from doing some shit like that?
呃 我是说
I mean
你能做得了什么
What are you gonna do?
每日每分每秒盯着他吗
Stay with him every damn minute, every day you can?
他要是想 就总能找到方法
He gonna find a way if he wants to.
这不怪你
It ain't on you.
这不怪你 如果是你的错我会跟你说的
It ain't on you. I would tell you if it was.
其他的事处理得怎样了 伙计?
What's up with that other thing, man?
还是一团糟 你Atlanta的朋友 不知道啥叫纯货 我是说...
Still shit, man. Your man in Atlanta don't know what raw is.i mean...
- 我们得打折 - 你觉得我是Kmart店吗?(折扣店)
- We gonna discount it. - Do I look like Kmart to you, man?
- 我是说... - 你说什么 太可笑了
- I'm saying, I mean... - What are you saying? That's ridiculous.
重新分装然后都卖掉
Re-package it and sell it off.
你知道 Proposition Joe参加了葬礼
You know, Proposition Joe came to the funeral.
把我拉到一边 他有货源 人人都知道他有货源...
Pulled me aside. He's got a smoker. Everybody knows he's got a smoker...
他想跟我们分成 如果我们让出部分高层区
and he wants to share, if we cut him a slice of the Towers.
- 你知道 只是个想法... - 想想也不行 伙计 不行
- You know, it's a thought... - It's not even a thought, man. No.
我告诉你 我们会挺过去的 听到了吗
Let me tell you something. We're gonna get through all this, you hear me?
- 我知道 - 都会过去的
- I know. - All of it.
有什么出来了吗
Anything come out?
如果集装箱里是女孩 她们还在里面
If there were girls in that can, they're still inside.
- 你们想把监听装置安在哪 - 码头工会的电话
- Your DNRs go where? - Phones for dockworkers local.
办公室 几个工会干事的私人电话
Offices, personal phones for a couple of union officials.
看这 9581737是Thomas Pakusa的电话
Look here, 9581737 is listed to Thomas Pakusa.
2月4号还有3月16号...
On February 4th, and March 16th...
Pakusa接到Frank Sobotka的电话
our Mr. Pakusa received a call from Frank Sobotka's cell phone.
两次他都在第二天 跑到Talco公司的货船上作业
And both times, he works a Talco Line ship the next day.
两次电脑里都有一个集装箱消失
And both times, a can goes missing in the computer.
是其中有猫腻的有力证明
Pretty good argument for a conspiracy case.
- 什么猫腻 - 走私
- Conspiracy to do what? - Smuggle shit.
走私什么
Smuggle what?
组织女性偷渡到这来卖淫算不算
For starters, how about bringing girls here for purposes of prostitution?
- 这个我们都知道了 - 想要窃听还需要更多证据支持
- That one we know about. - You need to do better for a wiretap.
读读法典注释 窃听法案  第10节 406款...
Read your annotated code. Wiretap Statute, Subsection 10, 406...
在马里兰州可对指定犯罪活动的...
designates crimes where telephonic communication can be intercepted...
电话交流进行拦截 卖淫?
in the great state of Maryland. Prostitution?
你是说 如果一个人贩毒你可以窃听...
You mean, you can tap a guy's phone if he's selling drugs...
但如果他卖的是女人 就不管了?
but if he's selling women, he's out of bounds?
法律就这么定的
That's the law.
亲爱的 我回来了
Honey, I'm home.
看看双卧房
Start looking at the two-bedroom joints.
- 我们负担得起 - 怎么负担
- We can pay. - How?
- 找了个新工作 - 码头外?
- Got a new job. - Off the docks?
一周三四天
Three, four days a week.
为个希腊人做货仓领班
Warehouse foreman for this Greek guy.
他在Highland镇大街上有家电器行
He owns an appliance store down the avenue in Highland Town.
码头没事的时候就过去帮忙
I can work it around the hours that I pick up at the docks.
挣多少 Nick?
How much, Nick?
过来
Come here.
一周500左右
Like $500 a week.
也许更多
Maybe more.
但很稳定 你知道 我们有指望了
But steady. You know, we can count on it.
有你理发赚的和这些钱...
Between what you make with them scissors and this...
我们还掉车贷之余还有余裕...
we can pay down the truck and still have enough left over...
能在郡外找个好房子
for someplace nice out in the county.
1500块
$1,500.
给警察打折后是1250块
$1,250, with the police discount.
那东西挨不起现代都市犯罪环境
It just couldn't stand up to the modern urban crime environment.
好了 减速 就是这
All right, slow up. This is it.
这里是Nicholas Andrew Sobotka家 Reynold街1485号
It's listed to Nicholas Andrew Sobotka, 1485 Reynold Street.
Sobotka?
上面是这么写的
That's what it says here.
你没印象吗
That mean anything to you?
"瘪四" (美国动画角色)这就是我们要查的那个人的名字
Beavis, that's the name of the guy we're supposed to be working.
Frank Sobotka
Frank Sobotka.
但上面写的是Nicholas
But we got Nicholas.
就算在波兰小镇 你以为能有几个Sobotka?
How many fucking Sobotkas can there be, even down here in Polack town?
- 你知道这意味着什么吗 - 什么
- You know what this means? - What?
我承认一个旧毛球确实不是好的伪装...
It means old fuzzy Dunlop here is somewhat worse for wear, I admit...
但作为"线人"却开始有回馈了
it's really gonna start paying off as a confidential informant.
- 它妈的没门 - 你不想要回那1250块?
- No fucking way. - Are you out $1,250?
把我们目标和街道毒品交易挂上钩...
Because linking a street-level drug connect to our main target...
就值个2百块的情报费了
has to be worth $200 for starters.
听着 如果我向Daniels申请 他会怀疑的
Listen, if I try to register him, Daniels will smell a rat.
他信任你 Carv 你长得就值得信任
He trusts you, Carv. You got that trustworthy look.
你去 Lester 只能你去
It's you, Lester. Got to be you.
- 我? - 我们得把警督拖下水...
- Me? - We need to bring in the Lieutenant...
还有他的专案组 所有的人力和设备
his detail and all the manpower and toys that go with it.
Daniels听得进你的话
And Daniels listens when you talk.
你浑身散发着智慧的气息 兄弟
You got the smell of wisdom on you, brother.
- 我们各司其职 - 你的职责是什么?
- We all got roles to play. - What's your role?
我就是个有着大鸡巴的谦卑的混球
I'm just a humble motherfucker with a big-ass dick.
你自封得太过了吧
You give yourself too much credit.
好吧 我也没那么谦卑
Okay, then. I ain't all that humble.
真天杀的
I'll be goddamned.
我对天发誓 他要再敢播那首歌...
I swear to God, if he plays that goddamn song one more time...
我就要踹他屁股了
I'm gonna clock his ass good.
你能放倒他 Zig 他虚有其表
You can take him, Zig. He just looks big.
他它妈的谁啊 像个娘儿们
Who the fuck is he? All pussy.
你可是码头的传奇 Zig 他妈的传奇
You're a legend of the docks, Zig. A fucking legend.
你觉得我能放倒他?
You think I can take him?
你可以
You can take him.
- 有人受伤了 5号船台 - 谁
- Man down, berth five. - Who?
新Charles
New Charles.
- 救护车就过来 - 上帝
- Ambo's on the way. - Jesus Christ.
晚上卸货什么的最讨厌了
Night work with break-bulk. I hate this shit.
- 你们还要不要把这个搬开了 - 老天 靠
- You guys gonna move this thing or what? - Jesus. Fuck.
不该乱动伤者
Ain't supposed to move a guy when he's hurt.
轮到你中奖时我们会记得的
We'll remember that when you hit the number.
别在这秀鸡巴了 把那东西搬开
Quit pulling your dicks and get this thing off of me.
1 2 3
One, two, three.
Charlie 来 吸一口
Charlie, here. Take a drag.
救护车来了 Charlie
That's the ambo you're hearing, Charlie.
那边
Right over there.
别担心 孩子 你还在上班(算工伤)
Don't worry, kid, you're still on the clock.
Frank 那腿看上去怎样
Frank, how does the leg look?
- 哪条腿来着 - 先生 你能听见我说话吗
- Which leg is that now? - Sir, can you hear my voice?
握住我的手
Squeeze my hand.
我们把他抬上救护车
Let's get him into the ambulance.
各位请让一让
You need to clear the way for us, guys.
- 你们跟踪了集装箱? - 进了那个仓库
- And you followed the can? - Right to the warehouse.
- 监视车准备好了吗 - Kima今晚去办
- Surveillance set up? - Kima is on it tonight.
这案子值得细究 警督
This case needs to be worked, Lieutenant.
我知道一开始这只是个半吊子专案组...
I know it began for you as a bullshit detail...
但Sobotka牵扯了不少事 得由能干的警察来查
but this Sobotka's into some shit that needs to be worked by good police.
监听 复制电脑 我们已经找到了模式
The DNRs, the cloned computer. We've got the pattern.
Rawls找过我
Rawls came to me.
- 问我要不要接下谋杀案 - 你该答应的
- Asked if I would take the homicides. - You should.
那些女孩是在集装箱里窒息而死 她们确实死在里面
Those girls in the can really suffocated. They really died in that fucking box.
你要查这案子 就可以接那些谋杀案
You pick this case up, you might eat those open murders.
如果你不接...
But you let it pass...
就得扪心自问 良心上是否过得去
you got to ask yourself how you want to live your day-to-day.
地方工会的兄弟们捐的
From the guys in 15-14.
他会没事的
He should be all right.
你知道他怎么被叫作新Charles的?
You know how he got the name New Charles?
他第一天工作就遇上...
First day of work was the same day...
装卸桥把个舱盖掉在 Charlie Bannion身上
the Paceco dropped a hatch cover on Charlie Bannion.
我们不得不用铲子来清理老Charlie
Had to clean up old Charlie with a shovel.
从那以后他就成了新Charles
Ever since then, New Charles.
他会被截肢
He's gonna lose the leg.
Frank
钱是哪来的
Where's the money from?
我接下你的谋杀案
I got your murders.
但我要你有求必应
But what I need from you, I get.
不能敷衍了事 不能讨价还价
No bullshit, no arguments.
绝不讨价还价
No arguments.
- 你在浪费电池 - 又怎样
- You're wasting all the batteries. - So?
妈 他要把电池都用光了
Mom, he's wasting all the batteries.
你们再吵我就把那帐篷收了
You two get along or I'm gonna take that tent down right now.
- 告密者 - 蠢货
- Snitch. - Punk.
- 笨蛋 - 呆瓜
- Squirrel. - Mope.
- 闭嘴 - 谁教他们说这些的
- Shut up. - Who teaches them this stuff?
到我了 你老拿着
It's my turn, you just had it.
Elena
Elena.
不行
No.
我不相信你
I don't trust you.
我关心你...
I can care about you...
我想跟你成为朋友...
and I can want us to be friends...
如果你给我足够的时间 Jimmy...
and if you give me enough time, Jimmy...
也许我还会真心希望你开心
maybe I will actually want you to be happy.
但你让我怎样信任你
But how the hell am I supposed to trust you?
妈 快来 有蜘蛛
Mom, quick, it's a spider.
很大 满身毛
It's a big, hairy one.
- 天啊 - 快来 妈
- Oh, my gosh. - Come on, Mom.
如果把两案合并 至少能让Rawls帮我办事
But if the case does come together, I would at least have Rawls as a rabbi.
对我也有好处
It could still work for me.
你自己听听
Listen to yourself.
我爱我的工作 Marla
I love the job, Marla.
- 我不由自主 - 但工作不爱你
- I can't help it. - The job doesn't love you.
知道我最先爱上你的什么吗
You know what I love?
总是比我有远见的想法...
The mind that's always a step ahead of me...
和一直为我殚精竭虑
the person who never stops thinking it through.
我最先爱上的就是这个
That's what I fell in love with first.
你知道我最先爱上你什么吗
Do you know what I fell in love with first?
知道吗
Do you?
你的野心
Your ambition.
那个男人上哪去了
Where did that man go?